Renju R Karun

- **₹** Puthuval Puthen Veedu, Pathiripally, Mukkola Trivandrum, Kerala, India - 695043
- 1 +919895852653
- \bowtie renjurkarun@gmail.com

Summary

To be a key player on a highly motivated, productive and innovative management team wherein I could utilize my professional competencies to achieve the organization's collective goals and lead it to success, while enhancing and enriching my skills.

Core Competencies

- Strategic Planning
- Operational Excellence
- Research & Analysis
- Resource Allocation
- Solution Selling
- Competitive Intelligence Outbound Marketing
- Case Processing
- Project Management
- Team Leadership
- Communication
- Customer & Staff relation

Professional Experience

❖ Associate Consultant – Immigration {03.5yrs} Fragomen Immigration Services & Pvt ltd.

2014-2018

- Drafting Immigration process including H-1B, L-1B, L-1A, L-1B, H4 & B etc.
- Authenticate, evaluate and review applications and work permit related documentation.
- Conduct quality checks to ensure company's adherence to processes and protocols.
- Sorts, Prioritizes and Distributes mail and respond to general enquiries concerning area activities in accordance with established policies and procedures.
- Collect and verifies data and prepare and update recurring and routine reports.
- Create, maintain and update various information databases into the concern Lotus Notes CRM system
- Establishes and maintains record keeping and filing systems; classifies, sorts and files correspondence records and related documents and refers problem to management for resolution.
- Maintain a repository of all visa related documents for different clients. Oversees effective and timely delivery of end to end immigration services to valued clients.

Business Associate – Insurance {07 months} TATA AIA Life Insurance Pvt ltd.

2018-2019

- Review settled insurance claims to determine that payments and settlemnts have been made in accordance with company practices and procedures.
- Investigate, evaluate and settle claims and applying technical knowledge and human relation skills to effect fair and prompt disposal of cases.

Education

• BTech, Information Technology

2009-2013

School of Engineering, CUSAT Course completed in 2013.

• Higher Secondary Education

2006-2008

St.Mary's Higher Scondary School, Pattom, TVM Completed HSE – Science group with 75%

• Secondary School Education

2005-2006

St.Mary's Higher Scondary School, Pattom, TVM Completed SSLC with 72%

Activities

- Muthoot Corporate Cricket League Represented Fragomen.
- Infopark Corporate Badminton league Represented Fragomen.
- Unversity Cricket Represented College team.

Technological Proficiencies

• Microsoft Office Suite • Lotus Notes • Hubspot • VFS Global • Aiura

Personal Details

• Date of Birth : May 12, 1991

Gender : MaleCitizenship : IndianMarital Status : Married

Spouse Name
Languages known
English, Malayalam, Hindi & Tamil

• Passport Number : S3413378

Declaration

I hereby declare that all the above mentioned informations are true to the best of my knowledge and belief.